(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T09:38:26.254519",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire" 2nd Round of Concert Merch
[Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire" - 2nd Round of Concert Merch]
Attention For Visitors
[Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights and that cheering loudly is OK]
2nd Round of Concert Merch - ESSENTIALS PACK
Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire" 2nd Round of Concert Merch
[Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire" - 2nd Round of Concert Merch]
silly bakka, silly ba
シリアス な shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, gotta reckon ya
got a thirst for the worst look in' 馬鹿 な cheap-ass
Got a thirst for the worst look in' stupid, cheap-ass
silly bakka, silly ba
silly ass-looking shit, gotta shake it up
wanna be lookin' freaks, all they do is talk
getcha head out ya ass, like, what you got, huh?
毎回 毎回 神頼み
Every time, every time, praying to the gods
免罪 せん わ そんな 奴 に
No absolution for a guy like that
あー もう 情状酌量の余地なし
Ah, there's no room for mitigating circumstances
即死刑 はい
Instant death penalty, yes
地獄 まで お迎え なさ い
Go to hell right now
今 すぐ に お迎え なさ い
メラメラ burning all day
Mera Mera burning all day
真夏 の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 妬か れ て
Mera Mera, burning with envy
灰 に なる まで
Until it turns to ashes
メロメロ に させ て
Make me madly in love
さあ 踊り 狂っ ちまっ て
Now dance like crazy
火炙り パラダイス
Barbecue paradise
go up and down
silly bakka, silly ba
シリアス な shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, you know what i got
might be the pinnacle of cynical, but first keep the mic hot
and may i just remind you
act a fool, death's gotta fine you
c - a - double l, you already know
C-A-double L, you already know
scythe at the ready, slow and steady, give 'em a show
they wanna get real close, can't learn to let go
try ' n ' dance with her, answer to, look out below
Try 'n' dance with her, answer to, look out below
slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than rose
and slam ' em back ' til the sun rise and heaven 's closed
And slam 'em back 'til the sun rise and heaven's closed
sleep in ' ' til the next night, y ' all know where we go
Sleep in' 'til the next night, y'all know where we go
believe i still keep the tight shinigami flow
alright?
メラメラ burning all day
Mera Mera, burning all day
真夏 の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 妬か れ て
Mera Mera, burning with envy
灰 に なる まで
Until it turns to ashes
メロメロ に させ て
Make me madly in love
冥土 の 土産 に 舞う
Dancing as a parting gift to the underworld
that is all about
ほら まだまだ 足りない
Hey, it's still not enough
spent all day beneath the sun, sun, sun, sun
sub is blasting out, dan - dan - dan - dan
Sub is blasting out, dan-dan-dan-dan
i don't care, sing out, la - la - la - la
I don't care, sing out, la-la-la-la
one night this time, you don't gotta run, run
愛 は 痛い もん さ 苦しゅう ない 苦しゅう ない
Love is a painful thing, it's not painful, it's not painful
灼熱 に 飛び込ん で give it to ya, give it to ya
Jump into the scorching heat, give it to ya, give it to ya
エイヘム み ~ なさん !
Ahem, everyone!
you got the rest
mori ' s in the building so you know you ' re already dead, woo!
Mori's in the building so you know you're already dead, woo!
地獄 まで お迎え なさ い
Go to hell right now
メラメラ burning all day
Mera Mera, burning all day
真夏 の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 妬か れ て
Mera Mera, burning with envy
灰 に なる まで
Until it turns to ashes
メロメロ に させ て
Make me madly in love
さあ 踊り 狂っ ちまっ て
Now dance like crazy
火炙り パラダイス
Barbecue paradise
go up and down
WHO IS US, HUMANS?
WAKE US.
She who never imagined rising above it all,
Found the Abyss more beautiful than the heavens.
Step by step, she journeyed deeper,
Her story woven like a dark spell.
The Grim Reaper writes her Memoire.
silly bakka silly ba
Silly bakka, silly ba—
シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, gotta reckon ya
got a thirst for the worst looking in ' 馬鹿 な cheap-ass
Got a thirst for the worst, looking like a cheap-ass
silly bakka silly ba
silly ass looking shit, gotta shake it up
Silly-ass looking shit, gotta shake it up
wanna be look in ' freaks but do with talk
Wanna be looking freaks, but do with talk
getcha head out ya ass like
Get ya head out ya ass like
what you gotta hot, huh?
What you got a hot, huh?
毎回 毎回 神頼み（uh lalala）
Every single time, praying to gods (uh lalala)
免罪せんな そんな奴に (許し乞うたら?)
No absolution for a guy like that (Begging?)
あーもう情状酌量の余地なし
Ah, no room for extenuating circumstances
即死刑 はい
Instant death penalty, yes
地獄までお迎え なさ い
See you off to hell
uh, yeah, uh, uh, uh 今すぐお迎え なさい
Uh, yeah, see you off right now
メラメラ burning all day
Mera-mera burning all day
真夏の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 冬かかれて 灰になるまで
Mera-mera, scorched by winter until turning to ash
メロメロに させ て
Make me fall head over heels
さあ 踊り狂っ ちゃあっ て
Now, dance like you're mad
火炙り パラダイス
Roasted paradise
go up and down (ah)
silly bakka silly ba
シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, you know what i got
might be the pinnacle of cynical
but first keep the mic hot
and may i just remind you
act a fool, death 's gotta fine you
Act a fool, death's gotta fine you
ダンプル ドゥン ドンデ ダンダ ド デ
(Dum-pulu dun-don de danda do de)
c - a - double l
C-A-double-L
you already know
scythe at the ready, slow and steady
give ' em a show
Give 'em a show
they wanna get real close
can't learn to let go !
Can't learn to let go!
try ' n ' dance wit her , answer to , look out below
Try 'n' dance wit her, answer to, look out below
slaying to the beat , paint the street redder than rose
Slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than rose
and slam ' em back ' til the sun rise and heaven 's closed
And slam 'em back 'til the sunrise and heaven's closed
sleep in ' ' til the next night , y ' all know where we go
Sleepin' 'til the next night, y'all know where we go
believe i still keep the tight shinigami flow
alright ?
Alright?
メラメラ burning all day
Mera-mera burning all day
真夏の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 冬かかれて 灰になるまで
Mera-mera, scorched by winter until turning to ash
メロメロに させ て
Make me fall head over heels
uh 冥土の土産 に舞う that is all about
Dancing as a parting gift for the underworld, that's it
ほら まだまだ 足りない
Look, it's still not enough
spent all day beneath the sun , sun , sun , sun
Spent all day beneath the sun, sun, sun, sun
sub is blasting ' out , dan , dan , dan , dan
Sub is blasting out, dan, dan, dan, dan
i don't care , sing out la - la - la - la
I don't care, sing out la-la-la-la
one night this time
you don't gotta run , run , run
You don't gotta run, run, run
愛 は 痛い もん さ 苦しゅー ない 苦しゅー ない
Love is painful, no suffering, no suffering
灼熱 に飛び込んで give it to ya , give it to ya
Jumping into the scorching heat, give it to ya
み ー なさん ! you got the rest
Everyone! You got the rest
mori 's in the building , so you know your already dead
Mori's in the building, so you know you're already dead
umm , chi chika chi chika
Umm, chi-chika chi-chika
地獄 まで お 迎え なさい
See you off to hell
メラメラ burning all day
Mera-mera burning all day
真夏の 楽園
Midsummer paradise
メラメラ 冬かかれて 灰になるまで
Mera-mera, scorched by winter until turning to ash
メロメロに させ て
Make me fall head over heels
さあ 踊り狂っ ちゃあっ て
Now, dance like you're mad
火炙り パラダイス
Roasted paradise
go up and down
papara , para , para , para , para , para , para
Papara, papara, papara, papara, papara
papa , para , para , pa , papara , pa
Papa, papara, papa, papara, papa
(da-la-da, wo-foo)
冗談めいてっちぁってあては
Joking around like, ahaha
口説きまくってあたふた
Got into another argument
酸いも甘いも苦いのも
Whether it's sweet, sour, or bitter
飲み干せば alright
Drink it all down and it'll be alright
stand tough
not saints, nor sinners
man up, they say the winner takes all
ain't even sweatin' when the goin' gets rough
and not leavin' til' that last light
間違いさがし嫉妬仕方ないなきっと
Mistaking jealousy as just how it goes, surely
ココロ七変化なんて本物のおんもろだ
My ever-changing heart is a total piece of junk
好き手前の名前＝エンタメ、だめ？
Naming it just before liking it = entertainment, is that no good?
笑っちゃうのでも溢れ出すのはエモ
I wanna laugh, but what overflows is emotion
emotional wreck, but still I'm rocking high spec
with every live it marks survival, where the mic check?
we boast an out-of-this-world devotion, stay neck-and-neck
cuz when ya chips are down, ya cards are out, the queens own this deck
rhyme on my vibe
終わりはどうでもいいから期待させて
I don't care how it ends, so let me anticipate it
take you higher
聴かせてよ
Hear me out
we start fires
火照るまで
Until we're flushed
we're live wires
たまんないbeat
A beat I can't get enough of
underrated, honest
encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips
気付いてよ
Notice me
need a tip?
わかるとして
You know it
cuz we want it
解いてほしいのか
I want you to untie it
unfasten us and fascinate us
we can't wait faster, cuz
したい (da-la-da, wo-foo)
I wanna do it (da-la-da, wo-foo)
we want it all, and when I fall stay proud
without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい (da-la-da, wo-foo)
I wanna do it (da-la-da, wo-foo)
we want it all, and when I fall I'm gon' rise
I won't be your doll, but still I'm owning those eyes
ねえ面倒くさいとか言ったらそれは所謂終わりじゃん
Hey, saying something is a hassle means that's basically the end
why should I be tryin' for a dream that's a pain?
cuz death is dying every day designing rhymes for our gain, ya know?
zeroからegoまで count up
Count up from zero to ego
仕上がってどうざあたしの子守唄
Be ready and finished, here is my lullaby
「mellow」doesn't suit our vibe, steady flow in 'stellar
"Mellow" doesn't suit our vibe, steady flow in 'stellar
「still, still it's a thriller, keep ya eyes on your mori, fellas」
"Still, still it's a thriller, keep ya eyes on your Mori, fellas"
なんちゃって反省してんのかなんて嘘で
Acting like I'm reflecting on myself is a lie
引いて同情gotcha
Pulling in sympathy, gotcha
回してみて機嫌ガチャ
Spinning the mood gacha
当たるまで後悔
Regret until you win
what's that? stop feeling sorry
just an act. I still don't care!
...could maybe lay it down a million times
I'll get "fine" when I can get my share
save it for the night
足りない同士で「どうして」を灰にして
Turn the "why" into ashes with our lacking selves
(let's go)
death star shoot across the sky
we the bad guys, haha
お待たせしました shooting star
Thanks for waiting, shooting star
あたし cutie star 「カワイイ」もっとちょうだい
I'm a cutie star, give me more "kawaii"
tarinai, tarinai, ain't enough
it's alright, we still got a couple fights in us (you know?)
take you higher
聴かせてわ
I'll let you hear it
we start fires
火照るまで
Until we're flushed
we're live wires
キマっちまうbeat
A beat that gets me hooked
underrated, honest
encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips
気付いても
Even if you notice
need a tip?
おそいのか
You're too slow
cuz we want it
期待の向こうへ
Beyond the expectations
unfasten us and fascinate us
we can't wait faster, cuz
したい (da-la-da, wo-foo)
I wanna do it (da-la-da, wo-foo)
we want it all, and when I fall stay proud
without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい (da-la-da, wo-foo)
I wanna do it (da-la-da, wo-foo)
we want it all, and when I fall I'm gon' rise
I won't be your doll, but still I'm owning those eyes
hollywood
all dead beats here tonight and around the world
raise your hands up to the sky
here we go
行くこと聞かなきゃ振りかざす正義
If you don't listen, I'll swing my justice
世界見守る軍団の作意
The strategy of the army watching over the world
秘密めぐる怪し企み
Mysterious plots surrounding secrets
過去の記憶に隠された狂気
Madness hidden in memories of the past
信じるお気楽な次ぎ
The carefree next step to believe in
謎に満ちたりその夢のエネルギー
Filled with mystery, the energy of that dream
天才が魅せる世界の形
The shape of the world shown by a genius
どこへ向かう未来のシマエナガ
Where are we heading, future long-tailed tits?
hey, tired or just fossilizing, wanna run away?
'cuz I got the place where it's a safe space to rise and shine in today
last chance to realize inside my shores, don't be afraid
so cupcake
sonic rhythm float or fray the stellar beat
gonna grab and show the evil cast a spell on these streets
cuz judge me die
welcome to yoni yoni journey
wake up, we're gonna, gonna party
鳴り止まないステージの音楽しちゃって
Rocking the music on the unstoppable stage
からだはまだ元気, 参戦して頭はcrazy
My body is still energetic, joining in and going crazy
crazy, crazy, crazy
感嘆さ, 高々叫び
Filled with awe, shouting high
感者たちが待ち受けてる
The audience is waiting
まだまだ, まだまだ, キャリーヒューマン
Still, still, still carrying humans
参加者たちが大気中
Participants in the atmosphere
鮮やかなステージ, 賛成して朝までcrazy
A vibrant stage, agreeing and going crazy until morning
crazy, crazy, crazy
hey
Welcome to Yona Yona journey
wake up, we're gonna gonna party
alien life on this man-made planet, it's us
we don't gotta understand, it's our universe
say a curse on your fears, nah nah that won't fly
might a butch come a set us as we pierce the sky
pm to am, talkin' 25時
PM to AM, talkin' 25-ji,
see 'em soar into 永遠, let it free you slowly
See 'em soar into eien, let it free you slowly.
atmosphere can't hold me, but I'm chained by ephemera
back then, we really had it all
(oh, what a memory)
what I wouldn't give just to have it all back
remember how we lived
for that one house track?
killer vibes, you and I, sound illuminated disco-ball sky
ain't it worth a try, travel back in time tonight
painted summer sky, treble, bass, rhyme and light
up the stage, bring it back from the day
unlock the cage, crazy, sing it loud to blackout fade
Welcome to Yona Yona journey
Welcome to Yona Yona journey, wake up, we're gonna gonna party
我々は異星人 乗り取った派手な spaceship
We are aliens, taking over a flashy spaceship.
体はまだ元気 酸化で頭は crazy crazy crazy
Our bodies are still fine, oxidation driving our heads crazy crazy crazy.
簡単さ目指すは千里 kamchatka はまた beijing
It's easy, aiming for a thousand ri, Kamchatka and then Beijing.
まだまだ京浜 三冠馬さながら day trip
Still Keihin, like a Triple Crown horse on a day trip.
鮮やかな staging 賛成だ朝まで crazy crazy crazy, yeah
Vibrant staging, approved till morning, crazy crazy crazy, yeah.
我々は異星人 乗り取った派手な spaceship
We are aliens, taking over a flashy spaceship.
体はまだ元気 酸化で頭は crazy crazy crazy
Our bodies are still fine, oxidation driving our heads crazy crazy crazy.
簡単さ目指すは千里 kamchatka はまた beijing
It's easy, aiming for a thousand ri, Kamchatka and then Beijing.
まだまだ京浜 三冠馬さながら day trip
Still Keihin, like a Triple Crown horse on a day trip.
鮮やかな staging 賛成だ朝まで crazy crazy crazy, yeah
Vibrant staging, approved till morning, crazy crazy crazy, yeah.
Minor, wait a minute.
Wait.
Why do you have skin? Why do you all have skin? I'm confused.
No, don't tear it off. Not now. Not yet, at least.
I like to think there's a skeleton inside of everybody.
So just stay, stay as you are.
What's up, everyone!
Welcome to Mori Calliope's second concert!
And who am I, you may ask? Who am I?
Say my name.
Thank you so much for coming out, you guys. I have dreamed about this concert.
It's all I've been able to think about. I dreamed about the name, I dreamed about what songs I'd perform, I dreamed about what I'd look like, what I'd wear, and I dreamed about all of you.
Matter of fact, hold on, hold on a second. What was that that I heard? By the way, what was that people outside cheering 'Boat goes binted'? What's wrong with you?
Get a load of these boneheads. Oh, they're excited to be here. It's fine, it's fine. You guys are excited to be here. It's fine. Now, listen.
What did you guys think about Meta Meta? That was hot, right?
Now, listen, listen. Hold on. Something I want to address really quick. We were really worried about the wildfires that were going on here, right? We weren't sure if the concert was going to be able to be held safely.
But, you know what? At the end of the day, at the end of the day, right, we thought we have to do this concert, if we can do something to cheer people up, right? Cheer you guys up and do something fun together, and you know, get back to thinking about...
fun shit, right?
So, here we are. This is the very first time that we're doing a solo live in America!
I heard you guys—there, there they go. USA! USA! USA! USA!
Rather patriotic, very nice. But you know what? We actually have a band that came all the way from Japan...
glad to be here.
Give it up for those guys, and I want to introduce them to you as a matter of fact, all right?
So first of all, we have on the drums, it's Ishiyuuyah!
Kakuiine! Freaking cool.
Next up, on the bass, it's Iigo!
Ah, I'm jealous, man. So cool.
You know, I play a little bass myself, but I'm a beginner, so I'm very much like, ah, that's so cool. I want to be good at the bass someday.
Next up, we've got on the keys, it's Koshi!
Emoine! So emotional. Wow, my gosh, my heart is fluttering.
And last but certainly not least, on the guitar, we got Becky!
Kakuii! Everyone's so cool. Band saiko!
Yoroshiku onegai shimasu! Nice.
Now, now that I've introduced the band to you guys, we're ready to get into the details about how to have fun at the Mori concert.
Now, first, I want the whole venue to turn red, like the voltage of hell is going up. Come on, give me red, give me red!
And when this red runs black. Yeah, yeah.
All right. Now, listen to me, this is important. You turn the pen light into red when you feel super hyped, which is going to be all the time. But you know, if you overdo it, it's not as special. Kind of like, you know, solo lives are rare, we don't get to do them all the time, but they become more special, so use it only when you're super hyped, okay?
Now, let me hear something though, I want to know. Where are you from?
USA, USA, USA, USA.
Man, you vowned it! Crazily enough, crazily enough, the only the only state that I that I heard was Oregon. Why?
Man, you owned it! Crazily enough, crazily enough, the only the only state that I that I heard was Oregon. Why?
No, but then I got a little bit of everybody in there, so wherever you're from, thank you so much for coming out to see me. Um, it's very important to me. Thank you. You Deadbeats rock! You know that though.
Now, all righty, also here's the thing though, we don't just have people here in the venue, we also have people watching on the internet, on stream!
What's up guys? Hello. I see you, I see you. Hi. Hi, hi, hi, hi.
I'm looking at you. Deadbeat at home. Deadbeat at home, we love you, we miss you. Hi. That's us, they say. That's me, that's me.
Let's go. Now, you guys, they have so many different chants.
Chat, chat, chat, chat. Chat, chat, chat, chat, that's you guys.
Arigatou gozaimasu! It's ne, nice beat!
Yeah, chat, chat, chat. All right, time to stop that, time to All right.
Now that we've gotten that out of our system, you guys who are who are who are watching this stream have the opportunity to do the coolest thing right now. Post your impressions on Twitter, okay? #CalliMoir. No recording videos, but feel free to take lots of screenshots of me doing silly stuff and singing and performing, okay?
Now that we've gotten that out of our system, you guys who are watching this stream have the opportunity to do the coolest thing right now. Post your impressions on Twitter, okay? #CalliMoir. No recording videos, but feel free to take lots of screenshots of me doing silly stuff and singing and performing, okay?
But sadly, those of you watching on YouTube, I have some bad news for you. It's all over, the free preview is over.
And you know what? We haven't even gotten, I know, we haven't even gotten to like the sixth or seventh most hyped moment that's going to happen tonight.
So, bro gang, listen, I feel you. But, but, make sure that you check out the link in the description below, um, and see if you can, if you can, you know...
Cop your- Buy it! Yeah, I like that. I like that Deadbeat who was like, buy it! Yeah. You have the assertiveness I need.
Awesome, my freaking boneheads. Now then, listen up Deadbeats, we got to continue as much as I want to keep talking, so I can like chill for a minute. Listen, today I brought a bunch of songs here to harvest your souls. It's my job, don't hate me.
Don't hate me.
Are you ready to be soaked in Mori's music?
That's terrible.
I hate that.
I hate that that was the script.
Forget the script.
Let's just go crazy, right?
Right?
No script,
no script. We're just running it.
Next song!
Let's go!
無料パートは終了しました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！